ca86d93 | feat: Implement initial versions of Quality Indicator, Compliance Calendar, Training, and Staff features with supporting components and data.
cd4db05 | chore: Add Vite pre-bundled React and React DOM dependencies.
1cb575e | feat: Introduce a comprehensive staff management module with employee document handling and a utility for migrating document expiry dates.
a561129 | feat: Introduce a comprehensive staff management module with employee document handling and a utility for migrating document expiry dates.
